

Applicant for:

## Web Backend Dev(Java, OOP, Spring)

Dr.JOY 27 December 2020

# Việt Huy Nguyễn

Main interests: Java, Spring

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Tôi luôn đam mê việc học hỏi thêm các công nghệ mới cũng như rèn luyện các công nghệ đã biết. Tôi đã từng tham gia phát triển tính năng Single Sign On cho hệ thống Microservices gồm nhiều các services sử dụng công nghệ khác nhau và quản lý session khác nhau. Có khả năng giao tiếp trôi chảy bằng tiếng Anh ( Kì thi TOEIC không chính thức của Trường đạt 880 điểm )



# **Nguyen Viet Huy**

Java Developer

#### Contact

- 0329557548 | 0944037962
- huyviet.java@gmail.com
- HA NOI 100000

#### Education

2017 - 2019

Hanoi University of Science Technology - Global ICT

## Skills

**JAVA DATABASES ENGLISH REACTJS** 

#### About

Java Developer with 1 year experience in automation testing using Appium and 1 year+ experience in building web application using Spring boot. Familiar with SQL and noSQL databases. Able to communicate fluently in English with native speakers or read/translate English documentations. Big interest in learning new technology and improving skills

### Work Experience

#### Fullstack Developer

Present SAPO JSC

Fullstack developer using .Net Core, Spring boot, Spring MVC, ReactJs, NextJs

#### **Automation Tester**

2017 - 2018 LOTUS QUALITY ASSURANCE

Automating the testing process by using Java and Appium/Selenium's API

#### Freelance 2D Designer

**2017-2018** No Company

Designing posters, cover photos, standees and banners for events of universities like AJC, APD

#### **Hobbies**

Reading

**Bike Trips** 

Making music

Coding